mycitydeal.co.za 2013-05-09

# Up to 70% discount on restaurants, spas, travel, shopping - Groupon.co.za

### **We protect your personal information and data.**

**1\. Protecting You**  
The Groupon South Africa website, www.mycitydeal.co.za, is owned and operated by Twangoo South Africa (Pty) Ltd (t/a Groupon South Africa).

We have referred to Twangoo South Africa (Pty) Ltd in this document as "Groupon South Africa", "we", "us", or "our")

Groupon South Africa is committed to protecting your privacy and accordingly, we have developed this privacy policy (“Policy”). We will only use the information that we collect about you lawfully (in accordance with the Electronic Communications and Transactions Act 2002, the Consumer Protection Act, 2008, and other applicable data protection laws enacted in South Africa from time to time).

**Please read this Policy carefully. By accessing or using our Website, you acknowledge that you have read all of the terms of this Policy and our Website’s Terms and Conditions, and that you understand, and agree to be bound by, all the provisions in this Policy and the Terms and Conditions. If you do not agree to be bound by these terms, please exit this page and do not access or use the Website.**

Where this Policy uses a word starting with a capital letter, which is not defined in this Policy, that word will be a defined term in the Terms and Conditions.

Our Policy explains what information we collect on the Website, how we use and/or share this information, and how such information is maintained. This Policy only applies with respect to the information collected on the Website and not with respect to any information collected or obtained through other methods or sources.

Our Policy ensures that any information you provide us remains private and secure. We will never collect sensitive information about you without your consent. You can check and update the information that we hold about you by contacting us using the contact information below (and there may be an administrative fee payable for this) or by signing into the Website, and clicking on the tab marked “My Account”. If you find any inaccuracies we will delete or correct it promptly.

**2\. Personally Identifiable Information**  
We collect personally identifiable information ("PII") that is volunteered during the Registration process or in response to specific information requests explicitly presented to you.

We may also collect your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer this Website. An IP address is a number that is assigned to your computer when you use the Internet. Your IP address is also used to help identify you during a particular session and to gather broad demographic data.

We may ask for your e-mail address during your use of the Website. Also, to purchase Vouchers you may be requested to provide any or all of the following PII: first and last name, postal address, e-mail address, date of birth, telephone number and details of a payment mechanism, such as credit card details.

**3\. Use and Sharing of PII**  
All PII is retained by Groupon South Africa, in confidence and in accordance with applicable data protection laws in South Africa.

We use PII to provide you with information about Groupon South Africa, to properly provide you with the Service and for marketing ourselves to you.

In general, we may use the PII we have collected to:

  * • manage your account and provide you with customer support;
  * • conduct market research, and analyse your use of our Service;
  * • communicate with you;
  * • negotiate deals tailored to your specific location and interests; and
  * • enforce our Terms and Conditions.

Any financial or payment information, such as credit card details, provided to us for the purposes of concluding a transaction on our Website, will be used by us to process your payment for any voucher. This information may also be used to identify, and to protect you and us against, possible fraudulent transactions, and to generally manage our business.

**We will never sell or rent your PII to anyone else for their marketing purposes without your consent.**

However, we may pass your PII to our agents and subcontractors to help us with any of our uses of your data set out in this Policy. For example, we may use third parties to provide us with marketing or customer service assistance or send it to a credit card provider to process a payment.

We also always reserve the right to disclose PII in order to:  
(a) comply with applicable laws;  
(b) respond to governmental enquiries (or enquiries from a legal, governmental or quasi-governmental or local authority agency or Internet protection agency of any type);  
(c) comply with a valid legal process or procedure; or  
(d) protect our rights or property, this Website, and/or other users of this Website; or  
(e) fulfil any contractual obligations we may have in relation to your use of the Service.

Please note that as part of any PII sharing which we list above, we may send your information internationally. Different countries offer varying levels of protection of personal information. By submitting PII to us, you acknowledge that provided we have used your data in the ways set out in this Policy, we cannot be held responsible for any use of your data by third parties who receive and process your data. We undertake to make every effort to ensure that your PII is processed only for the purpose set out above, and for no other purpose.

**4\. Cookies**  
We use "cookies", a name for a specific technology used to register user preferences associated with the use of a particular website. A lot of websites do this, because cookies allow the website publisher to do useful things like find out whether the computer (and probably its user) has visited the site before. The information stored in the cookie is used to identify you and enables us to track the pattern of behaviour of visitors to the Website so that we can provide a more efficient and personalised service. You can usually modify your browser to prevent cookie use - but if you do this, the Service (and the Website) may not work properly.

In the course of displaying advertisements to this Website (if any), third-party advertisers or ad servers may place or recognise a unique cookie on your browser. The use of cookies by such third party advertisers or ad servers is not subject to this Policy, but is subject to their own respective privacy policies.

**5\. Emails**  
Please note that in terms of this Policy we may email you for one or more of the following purposes:

  * • as part of the Service. We may need to contact you for various reasons associated with the use of our Service, even where you have indicated you do not wish to be contacted for direct marketing purposes, and accordingly will send (or may send) emails to you in some of the following example circumstances: 
    * after Registration, notifying you of your account details;
    * as reminder emails about the services we offer (particularly if you have not used them yet or not used them for a while);
    * to send you information or Vouchers which you have asked for;
  * • as a newsletter;
  * • as promotional emails; and
  * • to offer related services to you from Twangoo South Africa PTY Ltd.

**However, in terms of any marketing or promotional emails we may send, we will always give you the chance to opt-out (or unsubscribe) from them in the future.**

**6\. Security and retention**  
We have put in place a number of measures to ensure that your PII is secure, including Secure Socket Layer technology to process payments, and password protection on user accounts. However, any one who may have access to your Groupon South Africa account will also be able to access your PII. Accordingly, we recommend that you do not share your password with anyone.

The PII which we hold will be held securely within our systems in accordance with our internal security policy and the law. We hold data until 3 years after it is last accessed or used by us.

Unfortunately, transmitting data over the internet cannot be warranted to be 100% secure. Whilst we take all reasonable precautions to safeguard this information, we may be unable to prevent unauthorised access to such information by third parties or inadvertent disclosure of such information during transit and we are not responsible for any actions taken by such third parties. You acknowledge this risk when communicating with and transacting on the Website.

**7\. Transfer in Certain Circumstances**  
If there is a sale, merger, consolidation, change in control, transfer of substantial assets, reorganisation or liquidation of Twangoo South Africa (Pty) Ltd, then, in our sole discretion, we may transfer, sell or assign information collected on and through this Website (including, without limitation, PII and other information), to one or more relevant third parties.

**8\. Non personal information**

In order to constantly improve the Service, we may use certain non-personal or depersonalised information that may be collected from time to time through your use of the Website or from other sources, to develop targeted advertising on our Website and on websites of third parties. This information may also be shared with third parties, including advisors, advertisers, suppliers and investors, for the purposes of improving the Service, and analysing the business.

**9\. Customer Service**  
If you have any questions or concerns, please feel free to contact us at [support@groupon.co.za](mailto:support@groupon.co.za).

**10\. Changes to this Policy**  
Please note that this Policy forms part of the Terms & Conditions for use of this Website and forms part of the Agreement between you and us. We review this Policy from time to time, to ensure that it reflects how we use your information, and accordingly we may, from time to time, amend this Policy, in whole or part, in our sole discretion. Any changes to this Policy will be effective immediately upon the posting of the revised policy on the Website.

In the event of any material change to this Policy, we will announce the change either: (a) on the home page of the Website, or (b) by email, if we have your email address. However, in any event, by continuing to use the Website following any changes, you will be deemed to have agreed to such changes. Accordingly, please review this page frequently so that you are aware of any changes.

This Policy was last updated on 29 March 2011
